Lesson 18. Everyone bakes cookies. Bob tells his family the cookies are selling well.
He asks his kids to help bake more cookies for tomorrow. Nicole says she's too busy to lend a hand.
The cookies are selling like hotcakes.
Way to go, Dad.
I need your kids to help out tonight with the cookies. We need another thousand by morning.
One thousand by tomorrow morning? That's impossible.
Amber and I will end a hand. She's a real night owl, so she won't mind staying up late.
Nicole, we'll need your help too.
Bake cookies the night before the elections? Nothing doing.
Lighten up big shot. You're running for high school president, not president of the United States.
Ted, you really get on my nerves sometimes.
Okay kids, let's stop fooling around. We need to get the show on the road.
We need to get the show on the road.